[Music]
Hey brother who is hey
play
heavy sweet hey so hey the
pugda is just a small
profit company
paadia the real
one Dangal's mother
ask
brother listen you will be
very lucky
you should also look at it
[Music] [
Music]
[Music]
Hey then fine come on come on come on no
no I have
given you all the money I will
pay you SG
soon
you will be fine
[Music]
check it is
fake [
Music]
then it is completely real and
[Music]
all the
blood is blood and
water [
Music]
[Coughing sound] [Laughter]
hey special deposit is not less
[Music]
[Music] [
Coughing sound]
[Laughter]
hey then from the water
you are also
quiet
special
you all the
real letter
give me the real one
please peace of mind I don't
want anything below 400
[Laughter] [Coughing sound]
Babuji do
it
ok heavy, it is
real  Khaba
[Music]
Hmm
Look, I have killed a
lot of people
[Music]
Hey Chandu, have you seen this, Madho
or [
Music]
who will keep the Kariya, if I feel like it, I will
not let you go,
you will not let me go
[Music]
Wow, it is very good, the sweetness will be
missed, I will miss it, it is
very good, see the story of the daughter-in-law, [Music]
Hey, this is my home, listen, come on, it is
very good, get it ready
[Music] Hey,
you just look, hey, I have
aunt's mango,
hey,
up
[Music] Hey,
daughter-in-law,
quickly get caught,
hit the moustache and make it red
[Music]
Uncle, after washing the clothes in the morning, who will hit the man,
hey, refuse, uncle,
you go, aunt, oh
God,
everything is
fine, if not, then
sorry, sorry, sorry,
listen,
listen, hi [
Music] [Music] [
Music]